redrobin.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | RedRobin.com

_Effective as of AUGUST 2009_

Red Robin Gourmet Burgers, Inc. ("Red Robin") has adopted this Privacy Policy for itself and its subsidiaries and affiliate companies. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and share personally identifiable information ("PII") we obtain from and about individuals located in the United States both online and off-line. 

### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY POLICY

When children under the age of 13 who are residents of the United States attempt to register at this web site, we will collect their e-mail address, first name and parent's e-mail address. (Please note that "parent" also refers to a legal guardian.). 

We will use the parent's e-mail address only to notify the parent that their child has attempted to register for a particular web site service, and to obtain the parent's consent to collect additional information from the child. We will give the parent the opportunity to prevent the child's registration with this web site. We will also provide parents, upon request, a copy of any information the child has previously provided to us, and the opportunity to edit or delete the child's information by returning to this web site at any time and [clicking here](mailto:privacyofficer@redrobin.com) to email your request to the Privacy Officer or by writing to the Privacy Officer at the address provided below. We will collect additional information from the child only if the parent gives us their express permission to do so. When we collect personal information from a child under the age of 13, we ask only for the information reasonably necessary to allow them to participate in the program for which they are attempting to register and for us to administer that program. 

We will not sell information we collect from children under the age of 13 that register on this web site to marketers or other third parties for commercial use, nor will we use it that information for purposes other than those you agree to at the time we collect that information. Instead, we will use the information to provide services requested by your child, such as sending them a birthday greeting and information about Red Robin contests and special promotions. 

If your child enters a sweepstakes or contest, we may use their information in the manner described in the rules for the sweepstakes or contest, and those uses may be different from the uses described in this Privacy Policy. 

### CHANGES

From time to time Red Robin may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of our websites, and technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, we will prominently post those changes in this Privacy Policy. You should review our Privacy Policy periodically so that you keep up to date on our most current policies and practices. We will note the effective date of the latest version of our Privacy Policy at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. 

### COLLECTION: COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ("PII") BY RED ROBIN

General. Red Robin collects personally identifiable information ("PII" -- that is, information such as your full name, e-mail address, mailing address or telephone number) in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you, it is because you voluntarily submitted the information to us in order to participate in activities, such as sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, chats or bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. We may also obtain PII from reputable third parties. 

Cookies. "Cookies" are small bits of information that the Red Robin website places on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on the site to make your visits to our website more enjoyable and valuable to you by providing a customized experience and recognizing your preferences when you visit our website. 

A cookie cannot read your personal data on your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. The only Personal Information a cookie can contain is information you supply as a visitor to our website. By accepting the cookies used on our website, you agree to give us access to information about your browsing behavior while on our website. We use this information to remember your personal preferences as well as to track overall user traffic patterns. We do this to determine whether the architecture of our website meets our guest's needs and the usefulness of the content of the website to our guests. You may set the preferences in your internet browser to disable (block) or enable (accept) cookies. You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent by a website to your computer's hard drive or to refuse cookies completely. 

If you've chosen to disable cookies on your browser, some of the functionality of our website may be lost. Certain other web pages that Red Robin produces, particularly those that require a login and password, require that cookies be enabled in your browser and cannot be used when you have disabled cookies in your browser. 

### NOTICE: RED ROBIN WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PII COLLECTION PRACTICES

When you voluntarily provide PII to Red Robin, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses we will make of the information. 

At the time you provide your PII, Red Robin will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII, including whether we may share it with outside companies (See "Choice" below). This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and that may want us to share your personal information with them, provided you have given Red Robin your affirmative consent to do so (See "Use" below). 

Sometimes we collect personally identifiable information from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or a paper eClub enrollment form. Providing detailed notice of this Policy in those situations often proves impractical, so in those situations, we may provide guests with a short notice that describes how to obtain from us the full text of this Policy and other relevant information. 

Red Robin's websites may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of those third party websites may be co-branded with a Red Robin logo, even though we do not operate or maintain those third party websites. Red Robin's website may also carry advertisements from other companies. Red Robin is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to our website. Neither are we responsible for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left the Red Robin website via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser website to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you. 

### CHOICE: RED ROBIN WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PII

Red Robin will not use the PII you provide to us for purposes different from the purposes we told you about when you submitted your PII. Neither will we share your PII with third parties who are not our business partners or otherwise not affiliated with Red Robin, unless we obtain your affirmative consent to do so. 

### USE: RED ROBIN'S USE OF PII

Red Robin will use your PII that you provide us under this Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If Red Robin obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy. If Red Robin materially changes its use of PII under its Privacy Policy, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which your PII was collected unless you consent to the change in Red Robin's Privacy Policy. 

Red Robin may share your PII with companies that are affiliated with us (that is, that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with Red Robin). Provided you have given us your affirmative consent to our doing so, we may also share your PII with parties who advertise their products and services on our website and with our franchisees who are not affiliates of Red Robin but would like to send you information about their products and services. For example, Red Robin may offer a sweepstakes or contest in conjunction with a co-sponsor that may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to Red Robin guests. However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with third parties when we collect PII from you. Moreover, we will never share your credit card information with third parties except those third parties that Red Robin uses to perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through Red Robin's website. 

Red Robin's team members, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII. Red Robin may share your PII with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses), but they may use your PII only to provide Red Robin with a specific service and not for any other purpose. 

There may be instances when Red Robin may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of Red Robin, other affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our website; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if Red Robin sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, Red Robin may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction. 

### SECURITY: RED ROBIN PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII

Red Robin uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII in Red Robin's possession and control against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, Red Robin uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete. Red Robin encrypts passwords and other sensitive information both in transit and when stored within Red Robin's online databases. 

### ACCESS: HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PII

Red Robin has implemented the following procedure that you may use to access, correct or delete your PII. 

  * If you would like to know the types of information that Red Robin collects from visitors to its website, please send your request to [privacyofficer@redrobin.com](mailto:privacyofficer@redrobin.com) or write to Red Robin at: 

Attn: Privacy Officer  
6312 South Fiddler's Green Circle, Suite 200N  
Greenwood Village, CO 80111

  * If you would like to know whether Red Robin has collected PII about you and what PII we have collected, please send us the activities that you participated in on our website that requested PII. After reviewing the relevant databases, we will confirm whether we have collected such information about you and provide a list of your PII that we have on file.
  * If your PII is incorrect, you may correct the PII by sending a written request for correction to Red Robin's Privacy Officer at the address above. Your request must include (1) all of the incorrect PII that you wish to change, (2) the corrected PII, and (3) your signature authorizing such changes. Red Robin will then correct the PII in our database and send a written confirmation to you. 
  * If you wish to stop all future communications from Red Robin, please contact Red Robin's Privacy Officer, requesting that we permanently remove your PII from any Red Robin database. We will send you a written confirmation of such removal. However, there may be residual information that will remain within our databases that may or may not contain PII. We will not give that residual information to any third party or use that residual information for any commercial purpose.

### REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: HOW TO CONTACT RED ROBIN ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS 

If you have questions or concerns regarding our collection and use of your PII or any other privacy issues, please contact: 

Red Robin Gourmet Burgers  
6312 S. Fiddler's Green Circle  
Suite 200 North  
Greenwood Village, CO 80111  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
Telephone: (303) 846-6000  
Facsimile:(877) 471-5691  
Email: [privacyofficer@redrobin.com](mailto:privacyofficer@redrobin.com)
